artbreak.com 2008-06-28

# Artbreak: Privacy Policy

## What This Privacy Policy Covers

This privacy policy pertains to the use of the Artbreak web site at http://www.artbreak.com. This privacy policy covers how Artbreak treats personal information that Artbreak collects and receives. People under 18 are not permitted to use the Artbreak service on their own, and so this privacy policy makes no provision for these people's use of the site.

Effective Date: 08/22/2007

## Information Collection and How it is Used

**General Information:**

  * We hate spam. We never sell or disclose your name or e-mail address to third parties.
  * Artbreak collects personal information when you register with Artbreak to use Artbreak services or to post content on Artbreak. When you register we ask for your email address and certain optional information such as biographical information, favorite materials and personal interests.
  *   * Artbreak automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie, and the page you request.
  * Artbreak uses information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, research, and anonymous reporting. IP Addresses IP Addresses are automatically reported by your browser each time you view a web page. Your IP address is stored in our user registration databases when you register with Artbreak. IP addresses may be used for various purposes, including: to diagnose or service technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP; to estimate the total number of users visiting Artbreak from specific geographical regions; to make sure that people are not voting for themselves or friends during contests or promotions.

## Service-related Announcements

We will send you a welcome/confirmation email when you sign up for our services. Receipt of this email is required for using our services.

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account by emailing support@artbreak.com from the email address you signed up with.

## Choice/Opt-out

If you no longer wish to receive service communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by emailing us at support@artbreak.com.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use Artbreak products or services that require you to "sign in," and you may not be able to take full advantage of the Artbreak service. Artbreak uses its own cookies for a number of purposes, including to: Access your information when you "sign in"; keep track of preferences you specify while you are using Artbreak's services; display the most appropriate advertising banners, based on your interests and activity on Artbreak; estimate and report our total audience size and traffic; conduct research to improve Artbreak's content and services. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

When you post a message, your Artbreak ID or alias that you are posting under is visible to other users. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Artbreak may be required to disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the Artbreak Terms of Service. Artbreak may share demographic information with business partners, such as "74% of users who regularly use Artbreak are between 18 and 35" or the like. No personally identifiable information will ever be used without your permission.

Artbreak does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested or when we have your permission. It may be necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Artbreak's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. We will transfer information about you if Artbreak is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Artbreak will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the Artbreak web site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

As part of the buying and selling process on Artbreak, you will will obtain the email address and/or shipping address of other Artbreak members. By entering into our User Agreement, you agree that, with respect to other users' personal information that you obtain through Artbreak or through an Artbreak-related communication or Artbreak-facilitated transaction, Artbreak hereby grants to you a license to use such information only for Artbreak-related communications that are not unsolicited commercial messages. Artbreak and our users do not tolerate spam. Therefore, without limiting the foregoing, you are not licensed to add an Artbreak user, even a user who has purchased an item from you, to your mail list (email or physical mail) without their express consent.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

## Bulletin Boards / Chat Rooms

If you use a bulletin board or chat room on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

## Editing and Deleting Account Information

You can change your Artbreak Account Information (except your username), at any time. We may send you certain communications relating to the Artbreak service, such as service announcements and administrative messages, that are considered part of your Artbreak account. You can delete your Artbreak account at any time from your account page; however, please note that your identification, billing and contact information may remain in Artbreak's records for some period.

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. Your Artbreak Account Information is password-protected. In certain areas, Artbreak uses SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on your member account page or by emailing our Customer Support at support@artbreak.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). To learn more about our SSL, follow this link. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at support@artbreak.com.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.

## Questions

If you have questions or suggestions you can contact us at:  
Artbreak Customer Care - Privacy Policy  
260 Perkins St #3E, Oakland, CA 94610 - (510) 393-5057
